# **Curriculum Vitae**



## **Ervina Fernandes**

BACHELOR OF ARTS (S,Sn), PETRA CHRISTIAN UNIVERSITY, SURABAYA

Contact Number: +6281 703332834 / +6281 216379494

Email : ervinafernandes@ymail.com ervinafernandes@gmail.com

Home Address : Jalan Galaxi Klampis Asri Barat 7/16

Blok H 2 - 2

Perumahan Galaxi Bumi Permai Surabaya 60119, Surabaya - Indonesia

Citizenship : Indonesia

Birth Place/DOB: Surabaya, 14 November 1991

## **Personal statement**

I am a self-motivated, hardworking and enthusiastic individual with excellent range of skills, knowledge and experience in Art Directing, Advertising and Photography industry. I am able to work and adapt to new situations and work well with new people. I have excellent track record of committed work ethic, team player attitude, excellent customer service, verbal and nonverbal communication skills, attention to details, efficiency and willingness to learn new skills and knowledge.

## **Education**

**2004 – 2007**Angelus Custos 1
Catholic Junior High School Surabaya

**2007 - 2010**St. Louis 1
Catholic Senior High School Surabaya

2010 - 2014

Visual Communication Design, Petra Christian University Surabaya

Latest GPA: 3.50, Latest CGPA: 3.27

## **Key skills**

- Vision and strategy planning
- Analytical and problem solving skills
- Cultural awareness and adaptability
- Verbal and nonverbal communication skills
- Inspire and innovative concepts making
- Networking and relationships
- Graphic design
- Advertising and art direction
- Photography

- Public speech, discussion, and debate
- · Willingness to learn
- Attention to details
- Approachable and professional
- Writing and story telling
- Listening and empathy
- Layouting
- · Corporate identity and branding
- · Digital Imaging

**Computing:** Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign.

**Languages:** Indonesian, Javanese, and English.

## **Work Experiences**

## June 2013 - August 2013

(Internship)

in 2H+ Photography, Commercial Photography in Jakarta

Worked as the photographer's assistant (Heret Frasthio and Henky Christianto, both of them are the commercial photographers and have professional skills and experiences in creative industry, expecially photography and digital imaging since 2004). This employment was an opportunity to develop knowledge in commercial photography working in the field, which was very valuable for me to understanding the selling point and attraction of "making of" photo to the consumers through the photography for the creative and advertising world. The clients such as: Sampoerna, Samsung, Aqua, Panasonic, Nutrilon, and the others products brands.

#### **December 2013 - Present**

Freelancer Photographer & Graphic Designer

### Award

On The Spot Scomdex 22 Photography Competition 2012 "Duo Japanese" **as the 2nd winner** 

On The Spot FBE Universitas Surabaya Photography Competition Festive 2012 "Young and Shine" **as the 1st winner** 

On The Spot Women Photo Hunting Competition 2013 "Live in Color"

On The Spot Photography Competition Festive 2013 "Back In Time"

## **Organization & Leadership Experiences**

#### Adiwarna 2012

Final Project Exhibition of Visual Communication Design UK Petra

### Bursa Buku

Books Exhibition of UK Petra

**"Write Your Own Story"**Story Telling Workshops at UK Petra

## **Personal interests**

My favourite hobbies are watching movies and travelling. I enjoy exploring new places, meeting new people and learning about different cultures and customs. I like all about fashion, photography, food and books.

See my online portfolio: www.behance.net/ervinafernandes